Answers to your questions in my own
words tell me about yourself. My
name is Burt Mahoney. I am a human
being. I have a background in
computers and fine art.
And I have been working in the
technology design and human
computer interaction space for 30
years. I have always been on the
front bleeding edge of what is
happening in technology for over 30
years.
I worked professionally through the
beginning of the internet web 1.0.
This is prior to 1998, before CSS
came out and was included in
browsers.
So I've been in the game a long
time, and I can tell you the AI
revolution happening right now is
very much like the old days of the
internet, except it seems even
faster than that was which is mind
blowing.
Thank goodness we have modern
social media to help spread the
word and keep things up to date.
So, I'm into music, I've been
listening my whole life. I like to
play darts. I'm a big fan of
English Premier League, and I am
trying to rebuild my life.
What kind of work do you do best, I
do best solving technology problems
for people. So if you have software
or you have some kind of process
that involves technology and you
want to make it faster, more
automated more whatever, I'm your
guy.
So, I do a lot of research,
investigation, a lot of q amp a
with people to really understand
what is the core of their problems.
So I'm quite thorough in
discovering and identifying the
right problem to solve.
And that's why I believe people
should hire me because I'm very,
very good at this, and I have an
ability to translate complex
technology and concepts and
strategies into layman's terms, or
if I discover what the person I'm
speaking to is fluent in, let's say
they're a tennis
player into real estate, or they're
a construction worker. I'll
immediately use analogy and
metaphor inside their domain of
expertise and parallel that to the
technology so their understanding
becomes instantaneous.
And they get quite enlightened so
people learn a lot when they work
with me.
And what makes my background
different is that I have been doing
this work longer than people that
are alive, doing this work
professionally right now.
I would say that someone with my
level of experience and skill and
design chops, I, I do have design
chops in eight different design
disciplines across 30 business
sectors.
So, I know how to design things.
Print, web, email, direct
marketing, annual reports, you name
it.
So, my background is that I'm a
generalist with hands on experience
across the board, and I'm a
specialist in that.
I'm a specialist in software, and
my expertise is communicating with
people to discover the true
problems to solve, and being a
translator between them.